That is why let's look at the stock creation of Lambert General Insurance Company, so the
first thing is
we never invest money in insurance companies,
okay, that too why, if you want to know then
definitely comment to me, then I will
tell you our question, okay, now the
growth will go away, okay, so if its
government career is over, then look at it now, if you feel like
learning, thank you, if you look at it then you can see it now and if you
look at the near future then you can see it now, okay, and if we
say five years here, then there is
a 22%, okay, and if we
say its maximum, then also there is 22%, okay, and its
highest price which it had gone, friends,
almost you can see its IS price, that it is so much, almost it went
up by 15029, so
this stock of animal Iman,
okay, see seven years ago,
after that it did not start so much, you
can see here, so what is it, on the
3rd of Chamber it had gone more than 1620 thousand sixteen hundred,
okay, so you have come, its pass
history, you must have got some information in the news, so for
now for today  That's all
anyone got with the video